[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "Because it's not as simple as simply 30,000 e-mails, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "Well, that's the real question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "She's not entitled to any diplomatic immunity like this, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "No, she's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["1:30 Eastern Time"], "PERSON": ["Suzanne"]}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "What were they really doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "And, Suzanne, we've just heard -- hearing tonight that the president will be giving a press conference tomorrow at 1:30 Eastern Time, which will be the first time he'd be, I guess, addressing this pretty contentious issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Can we expect any fireworks from that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I think you can expect fallout any time the president says anything, anything in Washington lately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night", "this morning"]}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "When did you last speak to David Petraeus?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I spoke with him last night and we exchanged some correspondence this morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "How would you describe his state of mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, I think his state of mind is fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Was there anything that goes into the territory of a potential security risk or anything of that nature?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "OYLAN: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Has he had any conversation or contact with Paula Broadwell in the last few days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Last few days, I'm not aware of any.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paula Broadwell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Petraeus", "Holly"]}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "How would you describe David Petraeus' relationship with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Well, I think very simply as close personal friends of not only David Petraeus but of his wife, Holly, as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress", "CIA"]}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Is he prepared to testify if he's called?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, that will be a discussion between him, Congress and the CIA, I would imagine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "I mean, from your discussions with him, does he believe that he personally did anything wrong in relation to what happened in Benghazi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "We haven't gone into any of those types of discussions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "And where do you see this going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Well, it's surprising that you have two four-star generals basically being removed from the scene this close together, and they both came from the same command.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Should we still be forcing out top leaders like David Petraeus for sexual shenanigans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "We can just decide not to.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", ":", "RB", ",", "CC", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Rick Francona, would you go along with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, and -- well, and -- well, you know, our European counterparts laugh at us when they see that we do this to ourselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Francona"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What do you think, Rick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I think we should be talking about a lot of other issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNPS", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "What exactly do you think he meant by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "The Democrats' base I think has largely been in some of the big population centers in the cities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "He can raise taxes if he wants to, can't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "There's probably a fair argument is what really drove the president's victory.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "Will you be chucking him over a cliff tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Do you think it's healthy for a biographer to be that close to their subject?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "But what would have happened, for example -- with one of your subjects, JFK -- what would have happened to JFK if e-mail and text messaging had existed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", ":", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["JFK", "JFK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Does it matter if they have affairs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "I think that's such a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "ELLEY: How about Churchill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I don't think Churchill ever had affairs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Why CNN?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Well, you guys called at a good time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "It's part food, which is obviously your most famous area of expertise, but also cultural travelogue, is that where you're going with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I think what we've found over the years shooting all over the world is that by virtue -- just by virtue of showing up with food just to see how people live and eat and drink as your only ostensible criteria, people show themselves to you, reveal themselves to you in ways that they often wouldn't to a hard news reporter, for instance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "In your world of chefs crazier and madder the better, I mean, infidelities is almost de rigueur, isn't it, along with wild drinking and everything else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "JJR", "CC", "NN", "DT", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "I think we -- he's a military man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Are you comfortable about -- you have done this before, but you seem to thrive on being around danger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I don't se myself as a daredevil.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "The love of food that you have, all things culinary, where did that come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "My family was food centric.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "``", "WRB", "JJ", ",", "''", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Have people woken up to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I think it's -- since I wrote that in \"Kitchen Confidential,\" things have gotten a lot better.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Which is the one you could easily or most easily stomach again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "CC", "RBS", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "The cobra heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iceland"]}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "What is the single most disgusting thing you have ever had to eat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Actually, it's the fermented shark in Iceland, their beloved national holiday dish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Who would cook it for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "First of all, if I'm facing imminent death, I think I would want to eat alone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Who is the greatest chef in the world, in your professional career?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "The greatest is a phrase I -- I don't know how to apply it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]